# GUILHERME ILLESCAS

23 YEARS

+55 (41) 99668-7097

oi@guilhermeillescas.dev

## GOALS

Helping others with my knowledge, transforming people's lives through technology and becoming a reference in the area.

### SOFT SKILSS

Time management;

Problem solving;

Organization;

Integrity;

Analytical view;

Good interpersonal relationship; Search for constant improvement;

Qualitative results;

## HARD SKILLS

React JS e Next JS

React Native

Node.js

HTML e CSS

JavaScript/Typescript

Git e GitHub

APIs RESTful

## LANGUAGES

English: Level B2 (Toefl)

# **SEE MY PROJECTS:**

www.guilhermeillescas.dev/projects www.blog.guilhermeillescas.dev

## SOCIAL MEDIA

- in linkedin.com/in/guilherme-illescas
- @gui.illescas (personal)
- @guilhermeillescas.dev (professional)

## **ABOUT**

I'm a developer who seeks to offer my best version, every day. Constant improvement and focus are factors that define me. I'm drawn to the React world and its vast possibilities. I love to make pleasant interfaces and offer the best user experience while working as a team to create a great integration and huge development to the organization.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### MID FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Escola Conquer | Sep 2021 - moment

Mentoring of team members for better technical and soft skills; Development of new features; Bug fixes; Development of new features and performance improvements in the Conquer Plus Platform

## **MID MOBILE DEVELOPER**

Dobank | Jun 2021 - Sep 2021 (4 months)

Development of new features in the app using React Native; Screen development;

## MID FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Chamer | Mar 2021 - Sep 2021 (7 months)

Development of front-end projects with React and Next js; Project review and refactoring; Consumption of RESTful APIs.

## **JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER & PARTNER**

WebCorp Br | Nov 2020 - Jan 2021 (3 months)

Project's organization; People and process handling; Application development in React.is and Node.is; DevOps

## JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

WebTrip Agência de Viagens | Jan 2020 - Nov 2020 (11 months)

Development and management of small projects; Management and basic server maintenance; Configuration and maintenance of web services; Process improvement and automation.

# **ACADEMIC EDUCATION**

• IGNITE - FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT (STUDYING) Rocketseat | 2022

# • SOFTWARE ENGINEERING (STUDYING)

Pontifícia Universidade Católica do Paraná | 2020 - 2023

## • CIVIL ENGINEERING (INCOMPLETE)

Pontifícia Universidade Católica do Paraná | 2018 - 2019